[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence",
    "options": [
      "Everybody have gone there",
      "Everybody are gone there",
      "Everybody has gone there",
      "Everybody has went there"
    ],
    "answer": "Everybody has gone there"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence",
    "options": [
      "The train is running in time",
      "The train is running on time",
      "The train is running with time",
      "The train is running to time"
    ],
    "answer": "The train is running on time"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Choose the correct preposition. My brother has no interest __ music.",
    "options": ["for", "in", "with", "at"],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Fill in the blank with right option. I am looking forward __ you.",
    "options": ["to seeing", "seeing", "to see", "to have seen"],
    "answer": "to seeing"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Choose the correct form (passive) of – “Who will do the work?”",
    "options": [
      "Who will be done the work?",
      "Who will done the work?",
      "By whom will the work be done",
      "Whom will the work be done?"
    ],
    "answer": "By whom will the work be done"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence",
    "options": [
      "I have looked for a good doctor before I met you",
      "I had looked for a good doctor before I met you",
      "I looked for a good doctor before I had met you",
      "I am looking for a good doctor before meeting you"
    ],
    "answer": "I had looked for a good doctor before I met you"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Fill in the blank with correct preposition. He is devoid __ commonsense.",
    "options": ["of", "from", "introduction", "at"],
    "answer": "of"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Select the right word. He ran fast lest he __ miss the train.",
    "options": ["can", "should", "could", "has"],
    "answer": "should"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The Arabian Nights __ still a great favorite.",
    "options": ["has", "are", "is", "were"],
    "answer": "is"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Choose the correct preposition. The police is looking __ the case.",
    "options": ["after", "on", "up", "into"],
    "answer": "into"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Choose the correct spelling.",
    "options": ["ascertain", "assertain", "asertain", "asartain"],
    "answer": "ascertain"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Select the correct sentence.",
    "options": [
      "The man was tall who stole my bag",
      "The man stole my bag who was tall",
      "The man who stole my bag was tall",
      "The man was tall who is stealing tall my bag."
    ],
    "answer": "The man who stole my bag was tall"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Complete the sentence with the correct verb form: ‘Neela __ her hand when she was cooking dinner.",
    "options": ["is burning", "burnt", "will burn", "was burning"],
    "answer": "burnt"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Choose the correct preposition. The tree has been blown __ by the storm.",
    "options": ["away", "up", "off", "out"],
    "answer": "away"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Identify the correct passive form of ‘He is going to open a shop’.",
    "options": [
      "He is being gone to open a shop",
      "A shop is being gone opened by him",
      "A shop will be opened by him",
      "A shop is going to be opened by him"
    ],
    "answer": "A shop is going to be opened by him"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Identify the correct synonym for the word ‘Magnanimous’.",
    "options": ["generous", "unkind", "revengeful", "friendly"],
    "answer": "generous"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Fill in the blank with the correct phrase: ‘__ your shoes before entering the mosque’.",
    "options": ["put out", "put off", "put away", "put on"],
    "answer": "put off"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Fill in the blank with the correct phrase: ‘He __ arrested if he had tried to leave the country.",
    "options": ["would", "could be", "would have been", "must be"],
    "answer": "would have been"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank: ‘Two of the children have to sleep in one bed, but the other three have __ ones’.",
    "options": ["different", "separate", "complete", "lonely"],
    "answer": "separate"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank: “The Democratic party’s candidate __ defeat in the small hours of the morning”.",
    "options": ["consented", "agreed", "accepted", "granted"],
    "answer": "accepted"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank : The proper function of the press is surely to - the man in the street with facts.",
    "options": ["deliver", "equip", "proffer", "provide"],
    "answer": "provide"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank : Since his retirement, Mr. Chowdhury, who was a teacher, has written four novels",
    "options": ["Already", "Formerly", "Presently", "Usually"],
    "answer": "Formerly"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank : I should appreciate it if you could complete  this work - Thursday.",
    "options": ["till", "untill", "up to", "by"],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Choose the right word to fill the blank : It will be your task to make sure the __ of traffic is maintained without interruption.",
    "options": ["circulation", "flow", "current", "procession"],
    "answer": "flow"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "‘Paediatric’ relates to the treatment of:",
    "options": ["Adults", "Children", "Women", "Old people"],
    "answer": "Children"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "The word 'Ecological' is related to-",
    "options": ["Atmosphere", "Pollution", "Environment", "Demography"],
    "answer": "Environment"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "The correct spelling is-",
    "options": ["Humorous", "Humourious", "Humourous", "Humorious"],
    "answer": "Humorous"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "A pilgrim is a person who undertakes a journey to a -",
    "options": ["a new country", "a bazar", "a mosque", "holy place"],
    "answer": "holy place"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "A person who write about his own life writers-.",
    "options": ["an autobiography", "a chronicle", "a diary", "a biography"],
    "answer": "an autobiography"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What is the meaning of 'White Elephant'?",
    "options": [
      "a hoarder",
      "a very costly or troublesome possession",
      "a black marketer",
      "An elephant of white colour"
    ],
    "answer": "a very costly or troublesome possession"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "If we want concrete proof, we are looking for - .",
    "options": [
      "building material",
      "something to cover a path",
      "clear evidence",
      "a cement mixer"
    ],
    "answer": "clear evidence"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "The light have been blown - by the strong wind.",
    "options": ["off", "up", "away", "out"],
    "answer": "out"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "As the sun - , I decided to go out.",
    "options": ["has shone", "shine", "shines", "was shining"],
    "answer": "was shining"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Maiden speech means-",
    "options": ["Late speech", "Early speech", "Final speech", "First speech"],
    "answer": "First speech"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "'Out and out' means-",
    "options": ["not at all", "brave", "thoroughly", "whole heated"],
    "answer": "thoroughly"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "He divided the money - the two children .",
    "options": ["between", "among", "in between", "over"],
    "answer": "between"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "No one can - that he is clever.",
    "options": ["defy", "deny", "denounce", "discard"],
    "answer": "deny"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Do not make a noise while your father -",
    "options": ["has slept", "is sleeping", "asleep", "is being asleep"],
    "answer": "is sleeping"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "He gave up - football when he got married.",
    "options": ["of playing", "to play", "playing", "play"],
    "answer": "playing"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "He has been ill - Friday last.",
    "options": ["in", "since", "on", "from"],
    "answer": "since"
  }
]
